craftelier.com 2016-12-31

# Privacy Policy

## Privacy Policy

**CRAFTELIER,** fully aware of the use and treatment that you should give personal data and under the existing legal regulations in this regard, has implemented a system to preserve the security, integrity and confidentiality of data considered personal.

This addition to fully comply with each and every one of the requirements set forth in Law 15/1999, of December 13, Protection of Personal Data, guarantees not only legal, but fair use of personal data and an adequate system to exercise their rights of access, rectification, cancellation and opposition provided in the aforementioned Act.

Contracting by the users of the services provided in this online store, imply the express consent of this for use, processing and transfer of data to all entities that directly and indirectly have professional relationships for the provision of that service.

**CRAFTELIER** host all personal data of its users in an automated file whose purpose is the management, control, prevention and maintenance of services to provide.

This file, meets all the requirements and guarantees provided in the legislation on data protection and which is responsible Asuncion Pizarro Villena. **CRAFTELIER** solely collect personal data of users, these at all adequate, relevant and not excessive. Users authorize an automated CRAFTELIER to treat your personal information and informing that it can contact the Department of Registration **CRAFTELIER** to exercise their rights of access, rectification, cancellation and opposition at the addresses listed for that purpose.

## Cookies Policy

All personal data requested on the website, are collected for the proper management of activities CRAFTELIER .: processing orders, shipping orders, information about promotions, et cetera. In no case they are used for other purposes or given to third parties. CRAFTELIER is clearly positioned against "spam", so under no circumstances use the personal data for sending unsolicited commercial communications without authorization.

From CRAFTELIER we wish to inform you that our website uses cookies to analyze user navigation.

Cookies are files that are installed on the computer from which you access our website with the purposes described on this page.

Description of the different cookies used in **craftelier.com** :

The application we use to collect and analyze information navigation is: Google Analytics: [www.google.com/analytics/](http://www.google.com/analytics/ "google analytics") y <https://www.google.com/intl/es_ES/analytics/learn/privacy.html>

The application we use to recommend items that may be of interest is BrainSINS: [www.brainsins.com](http://www.brainsins.com/)

We use cookies to Facebook and Twitter to show offers and promotions to our customers in the social network.

The application we use to provide online chat service is Zoopim: [ **www.zopim.com**](https://www.zopim.com/?z_campaign=AW_\[S\]_Brand_ES&gclid=CL_GjZDemMUCFUfkwgodrKQAwg)

The application for sending the newsletter is  **Sales Manago**   that uses the following cookies:

  * **SMCLIENT** \- unique identifier of the user visiting the web
  * **smuuid** \- random identifier of an anonymous contact visiting the web
  * **SERVERID** \- id server for load balancing
  * **smform display** -Parameters used to save the contact forms used in SALESmanago

We use cookies to **Google Adwords** remarketing.

In addition the following providers cookies are used to facilitate site navigation and site speed: **Bidswitch, Doubleclick, Adnxs.com, Openx.net.**

To allow, know, block or delete cookies installed on your computer you can do so by setting your browser options installed on your computer.

For example you can find information about how if you use as your browser:

Firefox from here: <http://support.mozilla.org/es/kb/habilitar-y-deshabilitar-cookies-que-los-sitios-we>

Chrome from here: [http://support.google.com/chrome/bin/answer.py?hl=es&answer=95647](http://support.google.com/chrome/bin/answer.py?hl=es&answer=95647 "Cookies Chrome")

Explorer from here: <http://windows.microsoft.com/es-es/windows7/how-to-manage-cookies-in-internet-explorer-9>

Safari from here: <http://support.apple.com/kb/ph5042>

Opera from here: <http://help.opera.com/Windows/11.50/es-ES/cookies.html>

Dirección postal:

CRAFTELIER  
C/ Real, Nave 110 -   
24199 Castrillo de la Ribera, León - España.  
Teléfono:   
Correo electrónico: [info@craftelier.com](mailto:info@mitiendadearte.com)
